<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type=«text/xsl» href=«style.xslt»?>
<content>
	<about>
	<paragraf>
		Like many other artists, I’ve been drawing since I was a little kid. I’ve always been passionate about reading comics, watching anime and play games. I was hungry about the visual art for death and I decided pretty early that being an artist was going to be my way of living. Reality didn’t allow it immediately though and I was forced into taking a degree in mathematical sciences before actually have ability to study only art.
	</paragraf>
	<paragraf>
		I personally pay a lot of attention to environmental storytelling in my works. I also wanted to pick something that is further outside of my usual comfort zone, since my main goal for the challenge was improving and expanding my skills in every aspect of the production pipeline. Usually, I have a soft spot for very whimsical and horror concepts, therefore my plan with this project was seeking concept art that has a more eerie and creepy vibe to it.
	</paragraf>
	<paragraf>
		From all of this I discover that I need to make a comics, cus it`s the best way to share my stories, opinion to others. So, i`ve made this page to introduce to you my universe.  
	</paragraf>
</about>
<storytelling>
	<story>
		Several years after the Order of the Sword incident...An unusual phenomenon suddenly appears in Red Grave City. A gigantic tree pierces through the surface in the middle of town, attacking with roots that drain the poor citizens of their blood.
	</story>
	<story>
		Two things come out of the mines: bodies and stone. They call him The Merchant of Bones, but he prefers to look upon himself as their saviour. In this, one of the darker fantasy short stories, if the mines fail, the city fails. If the city fails, the people will starve. He might be ruthless, his methods might be extreme, but he gets the job done. The people should thank him for it. Shouldn’t they?
	</story>
	<story>
		Verena has never known a time when her village hasn’t been under threat from the Maiden Thief. When her second sister is taken, Verena is blamed by her father but finds comfort in her sister’s lover, Jakob. The only question is, who will be next
	</story>
	<story>
		When Emily wakes up at the scene of an accident, she is shocked to discover that it’s her lying dead on the road. Although her death seems like a hit and run, Emily is determined to find out the truth. With no memory of how she died, the friends she has known for years all become suspects, and the only question is: who did it?
	</story>
	</storytelling>
	<bio>
		<Yaro>
			<text>
				Mystirious one.
			</text>
			<text>
				 In contrast to the more flamboyant Jo, Yaro is a quiet, calm, and relaxed individual. While V is generally polite to everyone he meets, Yaro is a man shrouded in mystery and does not speak more than necessary.Yaro possesses all of "Dead`s" knowledge of the Dead World and often reveals that he knows things that no human should have knowledge of, but does not explain how he attained such information, which only makes others more suspicious of him.
			</text>
		</Yaro>
		<Lady>
			<text>
				By this time, Lady Savalidy is seemingly living with Dante and working alongside him as a Devil Hunter. 
                                Lady enjoys a good fight, prolonging a fight with Lady for up to two days rather than telling her who she is 
			</text>
			<text>
				She began to develop emotions and compassion towards him, and eventually sacrificed herself to save him from Mundus's attack. 
                                After being revived, Trish joined Dante at his shop, and showed excitement at being his partner. By the time of the animated series, she has gone off on her own. 
			</text>
		</Lady>
		<Jo>
			<text>
				Jo is the Leader of the Southes.He overcame battle after arduous battle in his past, 
                                and currently serves as a barrier to any attempt by demons to invade his world. 
                                Dante greets any and all challengers with a signature smile on his face.
			</text>
			<text>
				He often borrows from Lady, and often attempts to gamble to repay his debts to her and others. 
                                However, he has extremely bad luck with all forms of gambling, even with something as simple as a coin toss, 
                                and loses any game not involved with demon hunting. 
                                As a result, he is deep in debt to Lady, and is often left with no money at all after she takes her cut.
			</text>
		</Jo>
	</bio>
	<student>
		<name> Bobolia Kseniya</name>
		<faculty>Faculty of Information Technology</faculty>
		<spezialisation> 2 course of Desiqng of electronic and web publication, 12 group</spezialisation>
		<year>2020</year>
	</student>
</content>
